<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup Idea on A ML engineer</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/startup-idea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup Idea on A ML engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:16:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/startup-idea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Indian English Movies</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/indian-english-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:16:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/indian-english-movies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a whole generation of children and young adults in India who are proficient only in English with very minimal local language exposure (bcoz&amp;hellip; mandatory in school!).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are from India 1 - parents are affluent and they attend a top school. Entertainment for them is k-pop and western series (netflix/prime/hotstar etc).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a niche market to create Indian English movies and TV series. They may be quite small right now - but that will grow to a sizeable number within a decade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting Enterprise Search</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We, human beings, are quite good at processing new information, but are &lt;em&gt;terrible&lt;/em&gt; in storing them in long-term memory(LTM). LTM is finite and very limited. Many centuries ago, the printing press took a giant step in alleviating this problem. And then, distribution boomed. The number of printed content exploded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Humans are a sucker for information&lt;/em&gt;. How do you &lt;em&gt;find&lt;/em&gt; if the information you are searching for exist in that book? &lt;em&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/em&gt; listed the broad topic areas covered in the book. But a 300+ pages book has lot more keywords. This resulted in &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;index&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. Added to the end of the book, index provided a quick lookup on the word and the page(s) where it was discussed/explained.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
