<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bargava Subramanian on A ML engineer</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bargava Subramanian on A ML engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 12:27:33 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Need Grammarly for Design</title>
      <link>/blog/grammarly-for-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/grammarly-for-design/</guid>
      <description>“Once you can name something, you’re conscious of it. You have power over it. You’re in control. You own it.”
 Robin Williams
I am a technical co-founder at a startup. But then, I also spend a lot of time writing and designing - emails, content marketing, decks, updates to clients, dashboards, product feedback, product features - and the list goes on. These are non-traditional tasks for me; tasks that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t done much in my corporate career and I don&amp;rsquo;t have academic training in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I learned to suck less at Chess</title>
      <link>/blog/suck-less-at-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/suck-less-at-chess/</guid>
      <description>Access to knowledge isn’t nearly as difficult as the desire to learn Seth Godin
 Growing up and going to school in the 1980s in the cold, sleepy town Ooty, weekends were not very exciting. One activity I looked forward to was poring over the weekly Saturday Sports Special edition that came with the English daily newspaper we got. It had two chess puzzles. And I used to spend a good hour or two that weekend trying to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting Enterprise Search</title>
      <link>/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</guid>
      <description>We, human beings, are quite good at processing new information, but are terrible in storing them in long-term memory(LTM). LTM is finite and very limited. Many centuries ago, the printing press took a giant step in alleviating this problem. And then, distribution boomed. The number of printed content exploded.
Humans are a sucker for information. How do you find if the information you are searching for exist in that book?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Crush it on Twitter</title>
      <link>/blog/create-twitter-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/create-twitter-audience/</guid>
      <description>source unsplash
David Perell and Matthew Kobach did a livestream on YouTube on &amp;ldquo;How to Crush it on Twitter&amp;rdquo;. Here are some notes from the session.
Who is the session for
Anyone who wants to create an audience on twitter.
Why bother about Twitter
 You can build a network solely based on your clarity and quality of your thoughts. Twitter is the instant writing improvement tool that has neer existed for mankind before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Crush it on Twitter</title>
      <link>/note/create-twitter-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/create-twitter-audience/</guid>
      <description>David Perell and Matthew Kobach did a livestream on YouTube on &amp;ldquo;How to Crush it on Twitter&amp;rdquo;. Here are some notes from the session.
Who is the session for
Anyone who wants to create an audience on twitter.
Why bother about Twitter
 You can build a network solely based on your clarity and quality of your thoughts.
 Twitter is the instant writing improvement tool that has neer existed for mankind before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 14:47:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Newsletter  Sign up to my newsletter to get regular updates to your email directly.  Past Newsletters Coming soon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 14:47:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notes/</guid>
      <description>Notes from content I consume  I listen to a good amount of talks and podcasts, read books and read a number of blog posts. In this section, I summarize my learnings. Build an audience on Twitter Why and how to build an audience on twitter? David Perell and Matthew Kobach did a livestream on &#34;How to Crush it on Twitter&#34;. Learn how to be a lighthouse for like-minded people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>Talks  Recent Talks Privacy-preserving models using Federated Learning Federated learning is a family of Machine Learning algorithms that has the core idea: a connected network exists in which there is a central server node. Each of the nodes creates data – that has to be used for training as well as for prediction. Each of the nodes trains a local model and only that model is shared with the server, not the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>Workshops  Recent Workshops Recommendation Systems using Deep Learning Recommendation systems play a significant role—for users, a new world of options; for companies, it drives engagement and satisfaction. We walk you through the different paradigms of recommendation systems and introduce you to deep learning-based approaches. You&#39;ll gain the practical hands-on knowledge to build, select, deploy, and maintain a recommendation system. More info  Details Venue: New York City, USA Date: Sep 2019   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>