<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My thoughts and learnings on A ML engineer</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My thoughts and learnings on A ML engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 09:31:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I learned to suck less at Chess</title>
      <link>/blog/suck-less-at-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/suck-less-at-chess/</guid>
      <description>Access to knowledge isn’t nearly as difficult as the desire to learn Seth Godin
 Growing up and going to school in the 1980s in the cold, sleepy town Ooty, weekends were not very exciting. One activity I looked forward to was poring over the weekly Saturday Sports Special edition that came with the English daily newspaper we got. It had two chess puzzles. And I used to spend a good hour or two that weekend trying to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting Enterprise Search</title>
      <link>/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</guid>
      <description>We, human beings, are quite good at processing new information, but are terrible in storing them in long-term memory(LTM). LTM is finite and very limited. Many centuries ago, the printing press took a giant step in alleviating this problem. And then, distribution boomed. The number of printed content exploded.
Humans are a sucker for information. How do you find if the information you are searching for exist in that book?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Crush it on Twitter</title>
      <link>/blog/create-twitter-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/create-twitter-audience/</guid>
      <description>source unsplash
David Perell and Matthew Kobach did a livestream on YouTube on &amp;ldquo;How to Crush it on Twitter&amp;rdquo;. Here are some notes from the session.
Who is the session for
Anyone who wants to create an audience on twitter.
Why bother about Twitter
 You can build a network solely based on your clarity and quality of your thoughts. Twitter is the instant writing improvement tool that has neer existed for mankind before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>